popspins.com 2019-04-20

# POP Spins

  1. **Introduction**

This Privacy Policy determines how your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is being used online. PII is described as information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. The following Privacy Policy informs how the Website collects, uses, protects or otherwise handles your PII in accordance with the Website.

  2. **Personal Information Collection**

When visiting or registering on the Website, as appropriate, the Website asks you to enter and stores your email address, your created username and your created password. This information is needed to facilitate the login process and enable the features of the Website.

The Website determines and stores your IP address in order to facilitate invite system and fairly credit for referring users.

The Website does not require any real names, physical addresses or person verification.

The Website does not require any payment information and does not process payments.

  3. **Personal Information Usage**

The Website uses the information collected from you in order to enable the features of the Website and personalize your experience.

Your created user name may be visible to other users.

The Website does not display your email address, full IP address or password to any of the Website users at any part of the Website.

  4. **Personal Information Changes and Erasure**

At any time you are free to change your email address or password.

You can irreversibly erase the stored email address or password at any time by changing them to random values. The previous values will be erased permanently as soon as the new values are stored. Changing the email address to a non-working one will permanently eliminate the ability to edit it again or to use the password reminder function. This is the fastest way to erase your information.

You can contact us _[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_ if you need further assistance with account erasure proccess.

The user name is non changeable in order to ensure consistent working of all Website functions.

  5. **Personal Information Protection**

We employ strict stored data protection measures.

The Website stores as little data as possible to ensure delivery of all our Website features. The Website does not require any sensitive personal data which could be used for making unauthorized payments or logins or to identify a person.

Passwords on the Website database are stored as cryptographic non-decryptable hashes.

By registering you acknowledge the risk of possible information leaks even when strict protection measures are applied. You must use only a non-sensitive information (e.g. unique password, non-personal user name and email) in order to prevent personal data theft.

  6. **Cookies**

The Website uses browser text files (Cookies). The Website or its service provider or a Third Party may transfer these text files to your browser's memory at any time during the usage of the Website. Cookies allow the Website to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. The Cookies are used to identify if you are logged in or made certain actions on the Website.

The Website uses third party (Google Analytics) Cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics tracking by using their User Opt-out system or browser plugin.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a Cookie is being sent in your browser settings. Turning off external Cookies will still allow you to access the Website. Turning off Website Cookies or turning off browser Cookies function completely will render some of the Website features not working (including signing up and logging in to restricted areas).

  7. **Third-party Disclosure**

The Website does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless you are notified in advance and give your explicit consent to do so. The Website may also release information when it is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  8. **Third-party Links**

The Website may include or offer third-party advertisements, products or services. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. The Website therefore has no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. All information entered by you on any of the third-party websites is subject to their own terms and privacy policy and this Website cannot be held liable for their usage of such information.

  9. **California Online Privacy Protection Act Agreement**

According to California Online Privacy Protection Act, the Website agrees that users can visit the Website anonymously. The Website includes a link to the Privacy Policy as well as Terms of Service on all of the Website subpages. Privacy Policy can easily be found on the Website and provides clear information on how personal information is collected and managed.

  10. **Children Online Privacy Protection Act**

The Website does not specifically market or provide services designed for children under the age of 13 years old.

  11. **CAN-SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

The website collects your email address in order to: send Website-related information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

The Website agrees to: not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses; identify the message as an advertisement if it is considered as advertisement; monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used; honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly; allow users to unsubscribe from advertisement emails by using the link at the bottom of each email.

  12. **Privacy Policy Changes**

The Website reserves the right to change Privacy Policy at any time by updating this page and without prior notice.
